[
  {
    "question": "picq1",
    "correctAnswer": "Aglet",
    "robotAnswer": "Peepil"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq2",
    "correctAnswer": "Barm",
    "robotAnswer": "Scrat"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq3",
    "correctAnswer": "Ferrule",
    "robotAnswer": "Cannus"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq4",
    "correctAnswer": "Glabella",
    "robotAnswer": "Twarf"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq5",
    "correctAnswer": "Nurdle",
    "robotAnswer": "Drob"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq6",
    "correctAnswer": "Obelus",
    "robotAnswer": "Rectan"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq7",
    "correctAnswer": "Octothorpe",
    "robotAnswer": "Prill"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq8",
    "correctAnswer": "Pappus",
    "robotAnswer": "Fauna"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq9",
    "correctAnswer": "Peen",
    "robotAnswer": "Pull"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq10",
    "correctAnswer": "Punt",
    "robotAnswer": "Rumble"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq11",
    "correctAnswer": "Tragus",
    "robotAnswer": "Lorne"
  },
  {
    "question": "picq12",
    "correctAnswer": "Zarf",
    "robotAnswer": "Swipper"
  }
]